=Wonder Wall=
=Episode 14=
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday.
(2018)
Zinuo,
from now on, eat whatever you want.
She won't control you anymore.
Starting today,
you're an adult.
You have to
make your own decisions.
And you have to learn
to walk your own path.
But no matter what,
I'll always support you
from behind.
Okay. Come on, eat.
It's good.
Go back to sleep.
It's not right.
That's not the taste.
Zinuo.
Zinuo, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Zinuo.
Are you okay?
Need some medicine?
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Zinuo.
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
(Tiezhu)
♪A villa by the sea♪
♪Seafood every day♪
♪Fancy cars, pick what I want♪
Hello.
Hello. Ming, open the door.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you tell us to come?
There is a big guy at the door.
Did you see him?
Yes.
He's just lying there.
Is he asleep?
I'll tell you the password.
Come in quietly.
Don't wake him up.
Otherwise,
it's going to get ugly.
Alright.
Sleeping like a pig.
Some surveillance this is.
Not professional at all.
Stop blabbering.
Let's go.
It's all here.
If you don't trust me,
you can count it.
Two million total.
No need.
Here's the receipt.
Fingerprint here.
Here.
(Personal Statement)
(Certificate)
Mr. Yu.
Ms. Wen.
You're so kind.
Give it to me.
Is it all there?
Yes.
How about we treat you to dinner?
No need. We've eaten.
You may go.
I'll take you
to the second floor.
Let's
- go?
- Go.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
This way.
Zhu,
is two million cash so small in size?
Fits in two bags?
Zhu,
this two million is heavy.
My shoulders are killing me.
Zhu,
I'm still shaking.
How could they
just give us two million like that?
It feels like a dream.
Stop blabbering.
What if someone hears us?
Alright.
Now hurry up.
Go.
♪Work hard and make money♪
♪I want to get rich♪
♪A villa by the sea♪
♪Seafood every day♪
Hello.
Yu Ming,
come to my car dealership tomorrow.
What for?
You'll know when you come.
It sings day and night.
Gives me such a fright.
That thing is gone today, alright.
Bring you weapon.
See if Hong Jinkui
is still there.
He has left.
Come on, take it slow.
- One, two, three.
- Okay.
Turn it.
Okay now.
Alright.
It looks pretty.
Welcome, Mr. Yu!
Why did you ask me to come?
Before Almighty God
and all
who stand here today,
I make this oath.
Today,
I want to take
the man who saved my son and me,
Mr. Yu Ming,
as my godfather.
As my sworn brother.
From now on,
We share honor and disgrace,
life and death.
My shop is yours.
My car is yours.
Pick one.
I... I have things to do.
I should go.
He did his deed and left,
seeking neither fame nor glory.
Do a great favor without expecting
any reward in return.
That's why I believed in him.
The sea may be cold,
but a warm heart makes up for it.
(School Awards Ceremony)
Your heroic deed
not only saved two lives
but also showed us
what true goodness looks like.
Thank you for your selfless bravery.
On a beautiful, sunny day,
you became a warrior.
With strength and wisdom,
you raced against time
and fought against death itself
to rescue us
from the grip
of danger.
You are an everyday hero.
A true guardian.
Students,
Yu Wenwen's father
is an everyday hero,
ordinary, but extraordinary.
Wenwen,
congratulations!
Okay.
Now let's welcome Yu Wenwen
to give us a speech.
Mom, tell dad to come back!
Tell him to come back!
He is out of strength.
Wenwen.
(To Mr. Yu Ming - A hero of our time.
Selfless courage. Eternal gratitude.)
Why do I have to give a speech?
I almost lost my dad!
Wu Xiaoxuan,
don't think you can live long
just because your family is rich.
Yu Wenwen,
you're a hero's daughter.
You aren't supposed to fight.
I'll go.
Are you okay?
It doesn't hurt.
I'm fine.
Stop laughing!
Don't laugh!
Yes.
I'm truly sorry.
Ms. Zhou,
We keep putting you out.
Yes.
We'll calm her down.
We will do it.
It's just
she is too stubborn.
Why are you back?
School gave her half a day off.
Perfect.
Jiang.
Don't freeze the beef.
We're cooking it now.
I'll help you out.
Alright.
Everyone's been praising dad today.
Why are you unhappy?
They kept talking about it.
When I think of that day,
I feel really awful.
It feels like...
It feels like
my heart is jumping to my throat.
It's just very painful.
You know,
your way of expressing things.
I should hire you a language teacher.
How about that?
She's way better than I am.
Let me ask you, why did you
pull Wu Xiaoxuan's ear today?
What did he do to you?
I said I was a bulletproof vest.
Whatever his dad did
will bounce right back to him.
He's lucky I didn't beat him up.
And now you really can't.
Your principal says
you've got an image now.
You're the daughter
of a hero.
So you can't get into fights.
See? Your dad can't take a compliment.
A hero's child can't beat others.
Does that child have no feelings?
No anger allowed.
Yeah.
People have feelings.
You can't just
shut them down completely.
Whatever happens,
you react accordingly.
If someone hits you, you hit back.
If they don't,
what if they get beaten to death?
Just look at yourself.
Let me
wash the pot later.
Mr. Yu,
you are really something.
I heard your mom tell me about it.
It scared me half to death.
That was terrifying.
He was like a coiled spring.
and then
he sprang out.
Aren't you afraid of drowning?
Mr. Yu,
from great peril
comes great fortune.
Welcome. This way, please.
What do you mean?
Stop being so paranoid.
I'm working. Can't you see?
Tomorrow,
dads and moms will be back.
Let's have dinner together.
I have no time.
See that guy at the counter?
I'm eighty percent there.
Tomorrow, we'll watch a movie together.
This could be a big night.
No way
am I letting a family dinner ruin it.
What would you like to drink?
It's on me.
I don't want anything.
Fine. I'm off.
Wait a moment.
I have a question.
Sit down first.
What is it? Hurry up.
I took your advice
and made her a bowl of noodles.
But she threw up.
She threw up?
Was it that bad?
She didn't even eat it.
She looked at it and got sick.
Then I doubt
it's the noodles.
What?
Maybe it's me.
Could be.
It means you don't really know her yet.
What should I do now?
She kept crying
in her room last night.
She wouldn't even talk to me.
Having some issues?
That's not necessarily a bad thing.
Right now, it's both a crisis
and an opportunity.
Can you be more specific?
Based on my experience,
- I think...
- Ouyang Qing,
coffee for No. 24 is ready.
My boyfriend is calling me.
I'll talk to you later.
Coming!
How did you make a girl cry?
You're really something.
You actually made a girl cry.
Listen to me.
Go apologize to her right now.
Hug her from behind.
And
whisper in her ear.
It's not what you think.
My dear mothers,
could you give me
some real advice?
Throw money at it.
Buy her bags.
Bags fix everything.
Crude, but effective.
That's so tacky.
Shiqi,
you can win her over with quantity.
Listen to me,
when you apologize,
look into her eyes.
Be sincere.
Admit your mistake.
When you praise her,
30% general.
70% specific.
Be genuine.
My dear fathers,
stop wasting my time.
Draw the game.
Draw it.
- Actually, I...
- Sorry,
It's not your job
to manage my feelings.
It wasn't your noodles.
It was my own problem.
Remember I told you
I caused somebody's death?
It wasn't drunk talk.
It was true.
Six years ago,
since I found
my mother was taking bribes,
I filed a formal report against her.
I thought if she went to prison,
my dad
and I
could break free from her control.
But things didn't go as planned.
The snowball kept growing.
More and more people got dragged in.
At last, my dad ended all this
by taking his own life.
But I can never
get over with it.
It just never ends.
It's on them.
Why must you
take it upon yourself?
And no one
knows what happened
back then.
In Unit 505,
at first, there was 30 million.
Then another 30 million was found.
Yu Ming and his wife
want you to help them
figure out what happened back then.
Maybe the answer
is on my other phone.
Before my dad's accident,
he sent me
a strange melody.
Look at the ingredients.
Let me tell you,
if you take a pill at night,
you'd wake up fully refreshed
the next morning.
Now I...
We both take it now.
Is that so?
Yeah. Look, he also takes it.
He doesn't need it.
He must.
Xiang just loves it.
Dad.
This...
This is my stepfather.
This is my dad.
They are my stepmother and my mom.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
She is my tenant.
Nuo, Chen Zinuo.
So this is
the girl you made cry?
So pretty. So delicate.
Shiqi falls a bit short.
Shiqi
is just a stick in the mud.
Just plain stupid.
Looks sharp,
but he is truly dumb.
He's really anxious.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
done face masks with us,
gone to the sauna, played chess with us.
All he wants is to apologize to you.
Yeah.
Did you
spend a fortune?
Will you just hush?
We've already talked it out.
Looks like we're not needed here.
I agree.
Let's go.
Go.
- Let's just go have our own fun.
- Come on.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
Shiqi,
keep safe.
those things in there.
Eat them
while they're good.
Let's go.
Don't wait.
For you two.
Hurry up!
Wait for me.
Don't mind them.
They're always like this.
They just got back,
so I'm the treasure.
Give it a few days,
I'm nothing again.
Being forgotten.
This is the surveillance footage
from Unit 505
after Yu Ming moved in.
Recently, a lot of people
came for Yu Ming.
Does he owe you money?
This money,
part of it is a reward,
part of it is hush money.
Don't ask questions.
I'm leaving then.
We've figured out
their routine.
When they're not home,
I'll go in and get that clock.
No need.
They've already thrown it away.
Any luck? Did you find it?
Not yet.
Keep looking. Over here.
Okay.
Well?
Didn't find it.
Search carefully.
Okay.
This is just
a very ordinary melody.
I can't tell anything from it.
It's a music-based encryption system.
Based on the seven note names,
plus sharps and flats,
you can represent
the 26 letters.
If you treat it like Pinyin,
you can spell out words
or sentences.
So how do you match them up?
First, find a reference point.
Sort everything based on that.
Then, use sharps and flats
on either side
to fill in the missing notes.
It's cool.
Who taught you this?
(2016)
Zinuo,
we all know
that Chinese Pinyin
has 26 letters,
but there are
only 7 musical notes.
Right?
But actually,
by changing the pitch,
from flat, to natural, to sharp.
Don't you think that could
match the 26 letters?
That makes sense, right?
Now I'm going to test you.
Can you
convey the words "I love you"
using these
music codes?
Write it down first.
I love you.
Give it a try.
So fast?
Correct?
Yes.
You're so smart.
Starting today,
these music codes
will be
the special ringtone
for your call to me.
Sure!
Alright?
I'm certain
this is the code.
He sent this to me
right before he died.
But I can't crack this part.
Each measure
is missing something.
It can't form
numbers or letters.
Is there any other way
to decipher this?
I've tried everything.
French, German,
and Japanese methods.
Mr. Yu.
Okay. Alright.
Thank you.
Your cello is fixed.
When I was fixing it,
I found the patterns on the cello case
were quite strange.
I studied them for two days
and found these patterned
should be related to music notes.
Look.
Here, this.
Every leaf
seems to represent a music note.
Before my dad's accident,
he sent me a strange melody.
I know
he was trying to send me a message.
But the piece wasn't complete.
Every measure
is missing something.
I've memorized that accompaniment.
Going by this chord,
this measure is indeed missing
some notes.
If we piece these together,
it'd be complete.
Right after the IEO,
so many people
a lot of people went all in.
Really.
With whales in the background,
a massive pump
is guaranteed.
We should wait
for a better entry
when it's more valuable.
It's like poker.
You can't just go all in blindly.
If you go all-in
on every hand,
you'll get trapped and you're done.
You need a backup plan, right?
Can't rush it.
Song,
stop eating.
This chicken is bad. My stomach's off.
Buy some better chicken
next time,
It tastes too bland.
Luckily, I didn't eat it.
This is
Michelin-level.
Mr. Wang,
Li Jin asked you to come here.
What's her purpose?
Before Chen Liyang committed suicide,
he left some evidence.
She got hold of it.
Right now,
she wants to use it
to blackmail me.
Well,
what should we do now?
Just wait and see.
First, let's see
what she will ask from us.
Is that Li Jin?
She has been released?
(Li Jin Verdict:
Guilty of Embezzlement, Five Years)
It really is Li Jin.
So she's out now.
♪Cuckoo♪
♪It has a quick temper♪
♪It becomes impatient in spring♪
♪Cuckoo, cuckoo, never stopping♪
That clock.
Cuckoo, cuckoo.
The Black Forest Clock.
Could your dad
have hidden any clues
in it?
What's wrong?
That clock has been thrown away.
It kept going off randomly.
So we threw it out.
Where did you throw it?
I want to see that money again.
I want to see
what kind of power it has.
That made my dad trade his life for it.
Oh, no.
Sir,
may I ask you something?
We threw away
a clock here.
Do you know where it went?
The garbage here
all goes to the dump east of city.
All the garbage
from this community
all goes to the east city dump?
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
You young people nowadays
toss things away
whenever you're upset.
And then afterward
you regret it.
Remember,
When you're
done searching,
put them all back neatly.
Okay.
Don't be like
those guys this morning.
There were people here this morning?
A man and a woman came in the morning,
brought about a dozen people.
Quite a big scene.
Oh, right.
They were also looking for something
sent from your Ziyu Garden.
Their car
was so shiny
and looked very fancy.
They seem to be quite rich.
What could they
have lost on earth?
They can just
buy a new one.
Being so wealthy,
why must they go
to all this effort here?
When they said Chen Liyang
was a huge embezzler,
I didn't believe it.
Even if he did embezzle,
Li Jin must have pushed him into it.
But now
I'm not so sure anymore.
When I reported Li Jin,
I never thought things
would blow up like this.
I thought if she just went
to prison for a few years,
my dad and I could finally
get some peace.
Even after everything fell apart,
I never thought my dad
was part of it.
Li Jin was right.
I was wrong.
I misjudged people.
I used to think
he was a good father.
But he made the same mistakes
as Li Jin.
He paid his life
to get this money.
Just how useless am I
that he'd find a way out
for me like this?
I know what my dad
has left me now.
It's the evidence
enough to send Li Jin
back to prison again.
He wanted to protect me.
He was afraid Li Jin would hurt me.
My dad handed me the blade.
Zinuo,
don't dwell on this right now.
We'll definitely find a solution.
Trust me.
Ming.
Li Jin already came by.
She took it away.
Got it.
That's right.
That's just like her.
Go buy me a bottle of water.
Okay.
Everything you cherished
are all here.
(Tomb of Chen Liyang)
Chen Liyang,
from today on,
we're even.
Mr. Chen,
sorry about this.
What are you thinking?
Li Jin ocne said
my heart is as hard
as a stone.
I think she was right.
We are the same by nature.
Just as cold,
just as selfish.
The harder I try to escape her,
the more I turn into her.
In the end, even I
can't stand myself.
Don't hate yourself.
You should love yourself.
Whatever makes you happy,
hold on to it.
Whatever makes you suffer,
either forget it
or get through it.
Haven't
felt this light in ages.
That's how it should be.
Actually, I don't think
you have to carry so much.
You don't know what happened
between them.
And it's them who made the mistakes.
That's not on you.
You should learn to let it go.
I can't be as selfless
as my father,
and I can't learn
to be as selfish as my mother.
Being stuck in between.
That's what's so painful.
A change of place
would do you good.
Out of sight,
out of mind.
Actually, I want
to go see my senior.
Every time, I feel lost,
she always knows how to guide me.
And when I'm with her,
I feel a sense of calm.
Isn't she in Germany?
I said change your surroundings,
not change your country.
How to say hello in German?
Hello.
How to say thank you?
Why the sudden interest in German?
If I have a chance to go there,
I can use it.
Thank you for being with me.
Thank you.
It's quite a challenge.
(Shengli Group
Equity Transfer Agreement)
(Mingcheng Times Project
Settlement Agreement)
(Shengli Group Fund Transfer Request)
(Payment Method)
(Lixun Equipment
Procurement Supplier Recommendation)
(Unknown Number)
Hello?
Let me speak to Ms. Li Jin.
Speak.
I have something
that I'm sure
you'll be very interested in.
(Shengli Group Fund Transfer Request)
On July 11, 2009,
One million yuan was transferred
to Weifang Engineering Company.
A shell company.
No real business at all.
In April, 2007,
you dared fake bids
for a fire safety renovation.
Every company involved
was a shell company.
Your quotes were more than double
the industry average.
You've got some serious nerve!
(Next Episode)
(Actor, Guo Jingfei)
Hi, I'm Guo Jingfei.
I invite you to watch Wonder Wall.
I'm not asking much.
Fifty-fifty.
No problem.
Li Jin did it.
She's the one who killed him.
I agree.
Hong Jinkui is one person.
We are a whole family.
If she doesn't die,
we'll die.
So what's our move?
We're surrounded now.
Everyone's after the money.
Get the old woman and the kid
out for me.
♪The road ahead is still so long
Where have you gone?♪
♪Under the blazing sun
I keep heading north♪
♪To those who pass me by
You don't have to look at me♪
♪Just keep walking your own way
I'll manage on my own♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪
♪Is the rain falling hard?♪
♪Is there someone
to hold an umbrella for you?♪
♪The wind has blown
the numbers off the signs♪
♪Where am I supposed to go?♪
♪Can I change my mind?♪
♪How do I go on without you?♪
♪When will this
endless rain finally stop?♪
♪Then I'll wait for you♪
♪Please don't leave me waiting♪